<problem display_name="Quick Quiz: Reporting bugs and security issues" markdown="&#10;&gt;&gt;What should you include in a good bug report?&lt;&lt;&#10;[x] Clearly state what the bug is: what behavior was expected, and what behavior actually occurred {{unselected: You missed one! Try again!}}&#10;[ ] Complain about the bug {{selected: This is not a correct response. Complaints would not be in keeping with the community standard of collegial, friendly conversations. Constructive feedback would be a better approach. Try again!}}&#10;[x] Clearly state how to reproduce the bug. This means that anyone else can follow the steps and see the bug for themselves. {{unselected: You missed one! Try again!}}&#10;[x] Provide screenshots (if the bug is user facing) of as much of the behavior as possible - or better yet, a video of a screen capture. {{unselected: You missed one! Try again!}}&#10;[x] State what system the bug was found on. Was it found on an Open edX instance running Redwood, or Juniper, or what? {{unselected: You missed one! Try again!}}&#10;[ ] Criticize the developers who introduced the bug {{selected: This is not a correct response. Criticisms would not be in keeping with the community standard of collegial, friendly conversations. Constructive feedback would be a better approach. Try again!}}&#10;[ ] All of the above {{selected: All of the above is not the best response, as there are two items that should not be included in a good bug report. Try again!}}&#10;&#10;" showanswer="" submission_wait_seconds="0" weight="1.0"><choiceresponse>
<label>What should you include in a good bug report? (Select 4)</label><checkboxgroup><choice correct="true"><div>Clearly state what the bug is: what behavior was expected, and what behavior actually occurred.</div><choicehint selected="false"><div>You missed one! Try again!</div></choicehint></choice><choice correct="false"><div>Complain about the bug.</div><choicehint selected="true"><div>This is not a correct response. Complaints would not be in keeping with the community standard of collegial, friendly conversations. Constructive feedback would be a better approach. Try again!</div></choicehint></choice><choice correct="true"><div>Clearly state how to reproduce the bug. This means that anyone else can follow the steps and see the bug for themselves.</div><choicehint selected="false"><div>You missed one! Try again!</div></choicehint></choice><choice correct="true"><div>Provide screenshots (if the bug is user facing) of as much of the behavior as possible - or better yet, a video of a screen capture.</div><choicehint selected="false"><div>You missed one! Try again!</div></choicehint></choice><choice correct="true"><div>State what system the bug was found on. Was it found on an Open edX instance running Redwood, or Juniper, or what?</div><choicehint selected="false"><div>You missed one! Try again!</div></choicehint></choice><choice correct="false"><div>Criticize the developers who introduced the bug.</div><choicehint selected="true"><div>This is not a correct response. Criticisms would not be in keeping with the community standard of collegial, friendly conversations. Constructive feedback would be a better approach. Try again!</div></choicehint></choice><choice correct="false"><div>All of the above</div><choicehint selected="true"><div>All of the above is not the best response, as there are two items that should not be included in a good bug report. Try again!</div></choicehint></choice></checkboxgroup></choiceresponse>
</problem>
