<problem display_name="Quick Quiz: Rerun Tests" markdown="&gt;&gt;Annoyingly, only Core Contributors to the project can kick off a rerun of a GitHub Action, but there are ways to work around this. If you’ve got a stuck or flaky test and want to rerun the tests, what do you think you could do to get a new test run?&lt;&lt;&#10;&#10;[x] Push a new commit {{Selected: Correct, this is something you could do to get a new test run.}}&#10;[x] Push an empty commit using git commit --allow-empty -m &quot;temp: empty commit&quot; {{Selected: Correct, this is something you could do to get a new test run.}}&#10;[ ] Close the PR and open a new one {{Selected: Incorrect, we want to preserve all history of a pull request and its discussion in one place, rather than having to follow discussion over multiple PRs.}}&#10;[x] Rebase the pull request atop master {{Selected: Correct, this is something you could do to get a new test run.}}&#10;[x] Squash commits, or reword a commit, using interactive rebase {{Selected: Correct, this is something you could do to get a new test run.}}&#10;[x] Close the PR and re-open it {{Selected: Correct, this is something you could do to get a new test run.}}&#10;&#10;" showanswer="" submission_wait_seconds="0" weight="1.0"><choiceresponse>
<label>Annoyingly, only Core Contributors to the project can kick off a rerun of a GitHub Action, but there are ways to work around this. If you’ve got a stuck or flaky test and want to rerun the tests, what do you think you could do to get a new test run? (Select 5)</label><checkboxgroup><choice correct="true"><div>Push a new commit</div><choicehint selected="true"><div>Correct, this is something you could do to get a new test run.</div></choicehint></choice><choice correct="true"><div>Push an empty commit using git commit --allow-empty -m "temp: empty commit"</div><choicehint selected="true"><div>Correct, this is something you could do to get a new test run.</div></choicehint></choice><choice correct="false"><div>Close the PR and open a new one</div><choicehint selected="true"><div>Incorrect, we want to preserve all history of a pull request and its discussion in one place, rather than having to follow discussion over multiple PRs.</div></choicehint></choice><choice correct="true"><div>Rebase the pull request atop master</div><choicehint selected="true"><div>Correct, this is something you could do to get a new test run.</div></choicehint></choice><choice correct="true"><div>Squash commits, or reword a commit, using interactive rebase</div><choicehint selected="true"><div>Correct, this is something you could do to get a new test run.</div></choicehint></choice><choice correct="true"><div>Close the PR and re-open it</div><choicehint selected="true"><div>Correct, this is something you could do to get a new test run.</div></choicehint></choice></checkboxgroup></choiceresponse>
</problem>
