<problem display_name="CC Work Types" markdown_edited="false" rerandomize="never" show_reset_button="false" showanswer="finished" submission_wait_seconds="0" weight="1.0"><choiceresponse>
<p>We often get questions about which types of work count as Core Contributor work. There is admittedly a blurry line at times, but often it is very clear. Review <a href="/jump_to_id/8c8f2a56764e499faaba831bd2b27958">"Finding Meaningful Work"</a> as a refresher.</p><label>Which of the following would count as valid Core Contributor hours? </label><checkboxgroup><choice correct="true"><div>Doing prep work for a Working Group meeting</div></choice><choice correct="true"><div>Attending a Working Group meeting, or catching up on a meeting (via recording or notes) if you can't attend synchronously</div></choice><choice correct="true"><div>Performing follow-up work from a Working Group meeting</div></choice><choice correct="false"><div>Working on projects for my company's client</div></choice><choice correct="false"><div>Meetings within my company's team about projects our company is working on</div></choice><choice correct="true"><div>Answering questions on the Open edX forums</div></choice><choice correct="false"><div>Giving a talk to my team</div></choice><choice correct="true"><div>Recording a talk on a topic relevant to some part of the community, and posting it for the greater community to see</div></choice><choice correct="true"><div>1-1/synchronous collaboration time with other community members on work you're doing together</div></choice><choice correct="true"><div>Working on a design, strategy, or other program that benefits the Open edX project but is not work that falls under my Core Contributor role (for example, working on translating the platform when you're a Product Manager)</div></choice><choice correct="false"><div>Using the knowledge or contacts I've gained through my Core Contributor role to try to gain new clients for my company</div></choice></checkboxgroup></choiceresponse>
</problem>
